Prince Sanji?
‫سانجي-ساما؟‬
What kind of guy is he?!
‫أي نوع من الرجال حضرته؟‬
All we know is what he looks like!
‫يُسهل تخيل مظهره‬
I heard he was still refusing to marry,
‫سمعتُ بأنه لا يزال يرفض الزواج‬
so I tried to teach him a lesson on Father's behalf.
‫فحاولت تلقينه درسًا نيابةً عن والدي‬
Just like the old days.
‫كما في الماضي‬
And this is what happened! He'll pay for this! Sanji, that bastard!
‫...لكن هذا ما حصل... لن أسامح ذلك الوغد‬
No, Your Highness, a hammer won't do.
‫كلا يا يونجي-ساما، المطرقة لن تجدي نفعًا‬
I'm gonna press it. Stay still.
‫سأضغط عليها، ابقَ ثابتًا‬
It's fixed.
‫عاد كما كان‬
So that's Prince Sanji!
‫هذا هو سانجي-ساما إذًا‬
Are you ready?
‫هل أنت مستعد؟‬
Anytime.
‫افعل ما يحلو لك‬
All right!
‫،إذًا‬
That's just what you'd expect from a wanted pirate!
‫هذا أقل ما تتوقعه من قرصان مطلوب‬
How dare you kick your real father!
‫كيف تجرؤ على ركل أبيك؟‬
Cut it out! You started this!
‫كيف تقول هذا وأنت من بدأ بالقتال؟‬
And you'd better stop saying that you're my father!
‫وتوقف عن إصرارك بقولك إنك أبي‬
You're my son who came back! Sanji!
‫أنت ابني العائد يا سانجي‬
Don't say that while you're attacking me!
‫أتقول هذا وأنت تهاجمني بالرمح؟‬
He's strong!
‫إنه قوي‬
He doesn't even have a raid suit on!
‫وإنه لا يرتدي بدلة الحرب حتى‬
I'll go back to my pirate ship as soon as the tea party ends.
‫سأعود إلى سفينة القراصنة حالما تنتهي حفلة الشاي‬
I'll just pretend to marry her!
‫سأتظاهر بالزواج بها فقط‬
You're still saying that?!
‫أما زلتَ تقول هذا؟‬
You just want the bond between you guys and Big Mom, don't you?
‫تريد صلة بينكم وبين بيغ مام فحسب، أليس كذلك؟‬
Then it doesn't matter where I end up!
‫لا يهم أين أقضي وقتي إذًا‬
You can't do that!
‫إن تصرفت بهذه الأنانية‬
It would be seen as the Vinsmoke family's betrayal!
‫سيعد هذا خيانة من قِبَل عائلة فينسموك‬
You think Big Mom would allow that?!
‫أتعتقد بأن بيغ مام ستسمح بذلك؟‬
I don't care what happens to you guys afterward.
‫لا يهمني ما سيحصل لكم‬
I just came here to protect my friends!
‫أتيت فقط لإنقاذ حياة رفاقي‬
You would forsake your own family?!
‫هل ستتخلى عن عائلتك؟‬
You guys are not my family!
‫!إنكم لستم بعائلتي‬
He was in the kitchen, as I thought.
‫كان في المطبخ كما ظننت‬
He was making food for rats again!
‫كان يحضّر الطعام للجرذان ثانيةً‬
Royalty mustn't cook.
‫أفراد العائلة المالكة لا ينبغي عليهم الطبخ‬
Shut up! Give it back!
‫اخرس وأعدها إليّ‬
Ouch...
‫هذا مؤلم‬
You idiot!
‫أيّها الوقح‬
Don't touch me!
‫لا تلمسني‬
He's so weak and pathetic!
‫ما أضعفه، إنه مثير للشفقة‬
We were all born on the same day!
‫وُلد أربعتنا في نفس اليوم‬
Why are you such a failure, while we're not?!
‫فلِمَ أنت فاشل هكذا بينما نحن لسنا كذلك؟‬
You failure!
‫.فاشلٌ لا يرجى منه‬
Are you beating up Sanji again?
‫أتضربون سانجي مجددًا؟‬
Help me!
‫ساعدني‬
Father!
‫أبي‬
Why?
‫لماذا؟‬
"Why?"
‫لماذا»؟»‬
I don't think you're gonna be a good soldier in the future.
‫لا أظنك ستصبح جنديًا جيدًا في المستقبل‬
I have no obligation to help you, and you're not worth raising.
‫لست ملزمًا بمساعدتك ولا تستحق التربية‬
Father!
‫أبي‬
You're a disgrace to our family!
‫أنت عار على عائلتنا‬
Stand up! I'll train you!
‫قِف، سأدربك‬
A disgrace to the Vinsmokes!
‫عار على فينسموك‬
Go ahead and make a charge at him, Yonji.
‫هيّا انطحه يا يونجي‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا‬
Did you remember something?!
‫هل تذكرت أمرًا ما؟‬
He blocked the blade with his leg!
‫صدّ النصل بساقه‬
To think the Sanji I knew can now use haki...
‫لا أصدق أن سانجي الضعيف ذاك يستخدم الهاكي الآن‬
Give me a sword!
‫اعطني سيفًا‬
Y-Yes, sir!
‫حـ-حاضر‬
Take it.
‫خُذ‬
What's wrong?
‫ما خطبك؟‬
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
‫ظننت أنني علمتك القتال بالسيف‬
I'm not gonna use my hands for such crap.
‫لن أستخدم يداي لمثل هذا التفاهة‬
My hands...
‫يداي‬
are for cooking only.
‫للطهو فقط‬
Oh, that weak little Sanji became this strong...
‫عجباه، سانجي الضعيف ذلك أصبح بهذه القوة‬
Cooking? That's absurd!
‫أقلت الطهو؟ يا للتفاهة‬
Do you still cook for rats? Royalty mustn't offer services!
‫أما زلتَ تطهو للجرذان؟ لا ينبغي للعائلة المالكة تقديم الخدمات‬
How embarrassing!
‫كم هذا مخجل‬
That's ridiculous.
‫لا ينفع معك الكلام‬
What problem do you have with this marriage?!
‫ما مشكلتك مع هذا الزواج؟‬
Generalissimo's hand-to-hand combat!
‫القائد العام في قتال التحامي‬
The fighting style of the man known as "Garuda"!
‫إنه أسلوب القتال للرجل الملقب بغارودا‬
It's a rare sight to behold!
‫هذا أمر لا تراه إلا نادرًا‬
An aerial attack? Ironically, this is my forte.
‫هجمة جوية؟ مثيرٌ للسخرية أن هذا موطن قوتي‬
Diable Jambe!
‫ديابل جامب‬
Collier...
‫كولير‬
Shoot!
‫شوت‬
War advances science!
‫عِلم الحرب المُتقدّم‬
Electromagnetic Crack!
‫الكراك الكهرومغناطيسيّ‬
Blaster!
‫بلاستر‬
The Germa that you once knew is a thing of the past now!
‫جيرما التي عرفتَها سابقًا أثر من الماضي الآن‬
Can I ask you something?
‫أريد أن أسألك سؤالًا‬
Do you think being a biological parent entitles someone to respect?
‫هل تظن أن الوالد البيولوجي يستحق تعظيمًا لكونه ذلك؟‬
You don't...
‫...لم تترك‬
have a single good memory of him... do you?
‫أي ذكرى جيدة، ولا واحدة حتى...‬
You...
‫...أنت‬
Father! Let me out!
‫أبي أخرجني من هنا‬
...suffered so much.
‫عانيت كثيرًا‬
Father! It's too dark!
‫أبي، المكان مظلم جدًا‬
Poêle à Frire...
‫بويله فرِير‬
You only have animosity toward him.
‫تبغضه أشد البغض، صحيح؟‬
Wall!
‫جدار‬
Hey, you guys, move!
‫أنتم، ابتعدوا‬
Electromagnetic...
‫الشافت الكهرومغناطيسيّ‬
You're tough as nails. I'm surprised.
‫أدهشتني، إنك صلب متين‬
I can't believe you're that weak little Sanji.
‫لا أكاد أصدق أنك نفس ذاك الفتى يا سانجي‬
This is getting ridiculous.
‫ازداد الوضع سخافة‬
I wanna attend the tea party and get out of here already.
‫أريد أن أحضر حفلة الشاي وأن أخرج من هنا بسرعة‬
Then I'm gonna be free from the curse of Big Mom's invitation.
‫بعدها سأتحرر من لعنة دعوة بيغ مام‬
I thought you might've changed a little, but you've actually gotten worse!
‫ظننتك تغيرت قليلًا ولكنك أصبحت أكثر سفالة من قبل‬
Get out of this room, old man! You're a stranger to me!
‫اخرج من هذه الغرفة أيها العجوز، أنت غريب عني‬
No, you have my blood in your veins.
‫كلا، دمائي تجري في عروقك‬
Don't get me wrong. All Germa soldiers are...
‫لا تسئ الفهم، جميع جنود جيرما‬
followers who are willing to die for the Vinsmoke family at a moment's notice!
‫أتباع مستعدون للتضحية بحياتهم من أجل عائلة فينسموك في أية لحظة‬
They're Germa's biggest military force!
‫إنهم أكبر قوة عسكرية لجيرما‬
Then, why don't you use them to make your stupid dream come true?
‫فلتستخدم جيشك هذا لتدرك طموحك التافه إذًا‬
Conquering the North Blue? Great! That's perfect for an evil organization.
‫تريد غزو الأزرق الشمالي؟ هذا عظيم عمل يناسب منظمة شريرة‬
You're quick on the uptake. That's right.
‫أنت سريع البديهة هذا صحيح‬
By joining hands with Big Mom,
‫بالتعاون مع بيغ مام‬
it'll become an objective I can achieve for sure!
‫سيصبح الأمر واقعًا لا خلاف عليه‬
An objective... I can achieve for sure!
‫أمر واقع لا خلاف عليه‬
If you can understand that, I have nothing left to say.
‫إن فهمت هذا فلا داعي لأن نكثر الكلام‬
I wanted to somehow settle this with you peacefully, but...
‫أردت تسوية هذا الأمر معك تسويةً سلمية‬
I need Big Mom's help, but the condition is establishing blood ties.
‫أردت قوة بيغ مام ولكن اشترطت عليّ إنشاء صلة بالدم بيننا‬
It's just a marriage,
‫ليس الأمر سوى زواجًا‬
but I can't let any of my precious sons marry someone from that crazy old bag's family!
‫لكن لن أبعث أي من أبنائي الغاليين عريسًا إلى تلك العجوزة الشمطاء المجنونة‬
Then I remembered... I have another son...
‫حينها تذكرت أن لي ابنًا آخر‬
who was a failure.
‫كان فاشلًا‬
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
‫إنك أضحية يا سانجي‬
I haven't changed.
‫وأنا لم أتغير‬
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
‫لا أعدّك ابنًا لي على الإطلاق‬
Hey, what are these?
‫أنتِ، ما هذه؟‬
You said your hands are important to you.
‫قلتَ إن يديك مهمتان‬
That's great.
‫هذا عظيم‬
Do you know the shackle collars that the Celestial Dragons' slaves wear?
‫هل تعرف الأطواق التي توضع حول أعناق عبيد التنانين السماوية؟‬
If they try to escape from their masters, they'll explode along with their heads.
‫إن حاولوا الهرب من أسيادهم، تنفجر رؤوسهم‬
Those work the same way.
‫هذه تعمل بنفس الطريقة‬
If you try to escape this island, your hands will be blown off!
‫إن حاولت الخروج من هذه الجزيرة، ستنفجر يداك‬
Screw you! Take them off!
‫سحقًا لكم، انزعيها عني‬
Big Mom had the foresight to lend them to me.
‫امتلكت بيغ مام البصيرة لإعارتها لي‬
She has the key.
‫وهي تملك المفتاح‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Don't do that.
‫لا تفعل هذا‬
You can't try to rip them off.
‫إياك أن تحاول خلعها بالقوة‬
Using the key is the only way to take them off, of course.
‫لن تُخلَع إلا بالمفتاح، طبعًا‬
You can't escape.
‫لا يمكنك أن تهرب‬
Well, first of all,
‫على أي حال، في الأصل‬
we Germa won't let you get away!
‫نحن الجيرما لن نسمح لك بالهرب‬
You have to get married!
‫عليك أن تتزوج‬
Extra! Extra!
‫جوار العاصمة - مدينة الحلوى‬
Boss Jinbe betrayed us?!
‫خاننا الزعيم جينبي؟‬
This happened between him and Mama yesterday?
‫حصل هذا بينه وبين ماما البارحة؟‬
Boss Jinbe was so cool when he stopped Mama's tantrum.
‫الزعيم جينبي كان رائعًا عندما أوقف نوبة غضب ماما‬
He blustered that he wanted to leave her crew,
‫لقد تبجح برغبته بترك طاقمها‬
but he got scared of paying the price and backed down!
‫لكنه خشيَ من دفع الثمن وتراجع‬
Yeah? That's pathetic!
‫حقًا؟ هذا مثير للشفقة‬
What a loser!
‫يا له من فاشل‬
I guess "Knight of the Sea" is only a title. I've lost respect for him.
‫يُلقَّب بـ«فارس البحر» دونَ سببٍ، فقدتُ احترامي له‬
So he was a coward and a traitor.
‫إذًا فقد كان جبانًا إضافةً لكونه خائنًا‬
Jinbe-san...
‫جينبي-سان‬
I didn't know you were working under Big Mom.
‫كنت تعمل تحت إمرة بيغ مام؟‬
That's why Fishman Island was protected by Big Mom.
‫لهذا كانت جزيرة البرمائيين محميةً من قِبَل بيغ مام‬
Jinbe is a former warlord, isn't he?
‫جينبي شيتشيبوكاي سابق، صحيح؟‬
I can't believe someone of his stature is her subordinate.
‫لا أكاد أصدق أن شخصًا بمكانته تابع لها‬
Brook, do you know this man?
‫يا بروك، هل تعرف هذا الرجل؟‬
Yes, he's a very important person to us.
‫نعم، إنه عزيز علينا‬
I must still complete that journey. Once I am able to move freely again,
‫عندما أقوم بالإيفاء بوَاجباتي وأتحرّر‬
I promise I will join your crew.
‫أعدكم بأنني سآتي للقائكم جميعًا ثانيةً‬
I guess he turned down the offer to join our crew that day,
‫أظنه رفض عرض الانضمام إلى طاقمنا يومها‬
because he wanted to fulfill his duty to Big Mom.
‫لأنه أراد الإيفاء بواجبه لبيغ مام‬
Now, this article... It doesn't sound like something he'd do.
‫لكن الموصوف في هذه المقالة لا يبدو جينبي إطلاقًا‬
He won't come and join us anymore?
‫ألن يأتي لرؤيتنا ثانيةً؟‬
Hey, Brook!
‫بروك‬
Please! I have to go somewhere!
‫رجاءً أحتاج للذّهاب إلى مكانٍ ما‬
Nothing is more important to you now than choosing a dress!
‫لا شيء أهم بالنسبة لكِ الآن من اختيار فستان‬
Stop being such a baby-s'il vous plaît, Madam Pudding!
‫توقفي عن التصرف كالأطفال يا بودينغ-ساما‬
But...
‫لكن‬
How about this dress?
‫ما رأيك في هذا الفستان؟‬
Wow, it looks good on you!
‫ما أروعه عليكِ‬
How about this one? I knew it, Madam Pudding! It looks wonderful!
‫وماذا عن هذا؟ علمتُ بأنه سيكون رائعًا عليكِ يا بودينغ-ساما‬
Everything looks good on you!
‫كل شيء يبدو جميلًا عليكِ‬
Which one do you like, Madam Pudding?
‫أيهما يعجبك يا بودينغ-ساما؟‬
Madam Pudding, do you know what the groom likes?
‫بودينغ-ساما، هل تعرفين ما يفضله العريس؟‬
Wait a minute, Pudding-san, what is she doing here?!
‫مهلًا يا بودينغ-سان، ما الذي يحدث؟‬
I guess she got caught by her attendants.
‫يبدو أن مرافقيها قد حاصروها ولم تستطع الهرب‬
I assumed she'd already led Sanji-san out
‫ظننتُها قادت سانجي-سان إلى الخارج‬
to meet with Luffy-san and the others by now.
‫للِقاء لوفي-سان والآخرين الآن‬
Looking at this, I bet Sanji doesn't even know that we're here.
‫بالنّظر إلى هذا، أراهن بأنّ سانجي لا يعلم بأنّنا هُنا حتّى‬
Then, who did Luffy-san see at the shore?
‫إذًا من رآه لوفي-سان على الساحل، من يكون يا ترى؟‬
I don't know. Maybe he just saw someone else.
‫لا أعلم، عساه رأى أخطأ الشخص وحسب‬
That's... If I'm not mistaken, he was on Big Mom's ship...
‫ذلك الرجل، أظنه كان على متن سفينة بيغ مام‬
Yeah, I know him very well.
‫نعم، أعرفه جيدًا‬
Baron Tamago!
‫تاماغو تعني بيض‬ ‫البارون تاماغو‬
Baron Tamago, may I speak to you?
‫بارون تاماغو، نود الحديث معك‬
What is it-soir ?
‫ما الأمر-سوارو؟‬
The Straw Hats' ship that stopped by at Chocolat Town yesterday...
‫سفينة قبعة القش التي رست عند مدينة الشوكولاتة بالأمس‬
They already know!
‫إنهم يعلمون بأمرنا‬
When they left, Mr. Pekoms, who was guiding them, was already gone, they say.
‫عندما غادروا، بيكومز-سان الذي كان يقودهم قد اختفى أيضًا‬
They know everything!
‫يعلمون كل شيء‬
As for the four Straw Hats who wandered into the Seducing Woods today...
‫الأعضاء الأربعة من طاقم قبعة القش الذين يتجولون في غابة الإغواء اليوم‬
Carrot's Poster: "Bunny Mink."
‫المكتوب على ملصق كاروت: مينك أرنبة‬
they're already cornered! As good as captured!
‫إنهم محاصرون، كما لو أنه مقبوض عليهم‬
Luffy-san and the others got caught?!
‫قُبِض على لوفي-سان والآخرين؟‬
But we still can't find the remaining two.
‫ما زلنا نجهل مكان وجود الاثنين المتبقيينِ‬
Pedro's Poster: "Leopard Mink."
‫المكتوب على ملصق بيدرو: مينك فهْد‬ ‫هذين الاثنين‬
That's us!
‫هذان نحن‬
It's leaked out completely! They knew everything from the start!
‫لقد انكشف أمرنا بالكامل، كانوا يعلمون بالأمر منذ البداية‬
Where were they watching us from?!
‫من أين كانوا يراقبوننا؟‬
That mink is not a leopard-soir.
‫هذا المينك لَيس فهدًا-سوارو‬ ‫المكتوب على ملصق بيدرو: مينك فهْد‬
He's a jaguar mink. His name is Pedro.
‫إنه مينك يغور اسمه بيدرو‬
Do you know him?
‫هل تعرفه؟‬
Just a little bit from the past.
‫قليلًا فقط من الماضي‬
I know what he would do-feuille.
‫أعرف ما قد يفعله-فويليو‬
– Anyway, I want you guys to look for Pekoms. – Yes, sir.
‫على أي حال، أرغب منكم البحث عن بيكومز - حاضر، سيدي -‬
Pekoms. Since he was alive-bon,
‫بيكومز، نجا وما كاد يفعل-بون‬
for the sake of our long-standing partnership,
‫لأجل شراكتنا طويلة الأمد‬
I was going to ask Mama to pardon him.
‫كنتُ سأطلب من ماما أن تعفو عنه‬
He gives me a lot of trouble-marron.
‫إنه يتسبب لي بكثيرٍ من المتاعب-مارون‬
We are in big trouble!
‫نحن في ورطة كبيرة‬
Hey, cut it out, junior!
‫اخرس يا جونيور‬
Quiet!
‫كن هادئًا‬
Oh, he's laughing! That's good!
‫شارلوت شيفون - زوجة بيجي - الابنة الـ22 لعائلة شارلوت‬
Good, good, good, good! You're a good boy!
‫جيد، جيد، جيد، جيد أنت فتى جيد‬
Hey, junior. I hope you'll become a great boss like me one day.
‫جونيور، آمل أن تصبح زعيمًا رائعًا مثلي يومًا ما‬
I can't stand watching that!
‫لا أتحمل رؤية هذا-غر‬
He's dazzling, isn't he?
‫إنه مبهر، أليس كذلك؟‬
He was just born.
‫حياته بدأت توًّا‬
And you're going to die.
‫وحياتك على وشك أن تنتهي‬
Don't you think it's an exquisite contrast? It's like a painting.
‫ألا تظن هذا تناقضًا جميلًا؟ كما لو كانت لوحة مرسومة‬
This is what you chose.
‫هذا ما اخترتَه أنت‬
Pekoms. I gave you a chance.
‫أعطيتك فرصة يا بيكومز‬
It didn't look like a chance to me.
‫لم تكن فرصة‬
Remember what happened to you on Zou.
‫تذكر ما حصل لك في زو‬
Human empathy isn't worth anything.
‫تعاطف البشر هراء لا فائدة منه‬
You're not cut out for this business.
‫أنت لست مناسبًا لهذا العمل‬
This is the perfect place for getting rid of someone.
‫هذا هو المكان المثالي للتخلص من أحدهم‬
Any last words?
‫هل لك ما تقوله قبل الموت؟‬
You underestimate Mama too much!
‫أنت تستخف بماما كثيرًا‬
Now, let me see your hands.
‫هيا، مد يدك‬
They're covered in bruises.
‫تغطيها الكدمات‬
Little eggplant!
‫أيها القزم‬
What's your problem, you damn geezer?!
‫ما خطبك أيها المُسنّ اللعين؟‬
Are your hands for fighting?!
‫هل لديك يدان حتى تقاتل بهما؟‬
Dammit!
‫سحقًا‬
I think I invested enough money, Caesar Clown.
‫أظنني استثمرت ما يكفي من النقود يا سيزار كلاون‬
Y-Y-Y-Y-Yes! And of course, I didn't stop researching!
‫نـ-نـ-نـ-نعم وبالتأكيد، لم أوقف أبحاثي‬
My dream is...
‫حلمي هو‬
for all races in the world to become family
‫أن تصبح جميع الأجناس في العالم عائلة‬
and sit around a dining table at the same eye level.
‫وأن يجلسوا حول مائدة الطعام سويًا‬
They'll drink what I drink,
‫يشربون ما أشربه‬
and eat what I eat!
‫ويأكلون ما آكل‬
Isn't that a wonderful dream?!
‫أليس حلمًا رائعًا؟‬
And you're gonna make it come true for me, Caesar!
‫وأنت ستحقق ذلك الحلم من أجلي يا سيزار‬
I want you to make my family members gigantic with the power of science.
‫أريد جعل أفراد عائلَتي ضخامًا بقوة العلم‬
You kept telling me
‫لقد أخبرتني باستمرار‬
that you were almost done, but needed a little more research money.
‫بأنك تكاد تنتهي، ولكنك احتجت إلى مال أكثر للبحوث‬
I was excited and spent quite a lot of money.
‫تحمستُ ودفعتُ كثيرًا من المال‬
So how're the results?
‫كيف هي النتائج إذًا؟‬
Well, thanks to you, they're quite good!
‫حسنًا، بفضلك، إنّها رائعة‬
The gigantification of the human body. Yes, I was doing experiments.
‫عملية تضخيم الجسد البشري، كنتُ أقوم بالتجارب‬
The whole world is looking for a technology like that.
‫العالم أجمع يبحث عن تقنية كهذه‬
But I was performing experiments to turn kids into giants. It was deadly.
‫لكن أبحاثي اقتصرت على تحويل الأطفال إلى عمالقة ولم أستطع أن أضمن لهم حياتهم‬
It's impossible to make a drug that'll magically
‫من المستحيل صنع عقار يحول البشر إلى عمالقة‬
make people gigantic like this old bag wants.
‫وكأنه سحر كما تريد هذه العجوزة الشمطاء‬
That's why I just screwed her out of her money, and...
‫لهذا خدعتها فقط لأخذ نقودها‬
called girls' ships over to the island every night,
‫واستدعيت الفتيات إلى الجزيرة كل ليلة‬
and spent all the money on alcohol and women!
‫وهكذا صرفت الأموال على الفتيات والخمر‬
Those were the good old days! I was going nuts behind Joker's back!
‫كانت تلك أيام العز، كنت أتصرف كما أشاء تحت حماية الجوكر‬
"Doflamingo Falls!"
‫عنوان الصحيفة: سقوط دوفلامينغو‬
I didn't expect Joker to be defeated...
‫لم أتوقع أن يسقط الجوكر‬
and my life to become this miserable!
‫وأن تصبح حياتي بائسة هكذا‬
Dammit! It was much easier back then!
‫سحقًا، كنت أعيش حياة سلسة سابقًا‬
This is all because of that...
‫كل هذا بسبب ذلك‬
Are you giving a facial performance?
‫هل تقدم عرضًا بتعابير الأوجه؟‬
No!
‫كـ-كلا‬
This! And that! And everything! This is all Straw Hat Luffy's fault!
‫هذا وذاك وكل شيء كلها خطأ قبعة القش لوفي‬
Big Mom! I was doing the research without sleeping at all!
‫يا بيغ مام، كنتُ أقوم بالأبحاث دون أخذ وقت للنوم لأجلك‬
And when it was almost complete,
‫كادت أبحاثي أن تكتمل‬
Straw Hat and Trafalgar Law showed up!
‫ثم ظهر قبعة القش لوفي وترافالغار لاو‬
If it weren't for them, the gigantism drug would've been complete!
‫لولاهما لكان عقار التضخيم اكتمل‬
Because I'm a genius!
‫لأنني عبقري‬
It's a shame that the lab built by the World Government,
‫من المؤسف أنّ المُختبر الذي أنشأتهُ حكومة العالم‬
and all its high-level technology, was destroyed!
‫بتقنيةٍ عالية المُستوى قد دُمّر‬
I could only achieve the results in that perfectly controlled environment!
‫يمكنني إحراز النتائج المرجوةِ فقط في بيئةٍ مثالية آمنة‬
The vast amount of money you invested and that lab!
‫الأموال الطائلة التي استثمرتها وذلك المُختبر‬
I lost them, so I can't create the gigantism drug now!
‫خسرتها جميعًا، لذا لا أستطيع صنع عقار التضخيم الآن‬
I can't!
‫لا أستطيع‬
I built the exact same lab as the one on Punk Hazard.
‫أنشأت نفس المختبر الموجود في البانك هازارد‬
I got the blueprints to it ages ago.
‫حصلت على مخطط البناء‬
Our minister of candy's amezaiku skills are quite versatile.
‫وزير الحلوى خاصتنا يمكنه صنع أي شيء من الحلوى‬
You can spend as much money as you want for the research.
‫يمكنك صرف ما تشاء من الأموال من أجل البحث‬
A-A-A-A... A-Are you sure?!
‫هـ-هـ-هـ-هل أنتِ واثقة؟‬
I mean, I appreciate it!
‫أعني، أقدّر هذا‬
So?
‫إذًا؟‬
"So?"
‫إذًا»؟»‬
When will it be ready?
‫متى سيجهز؟‬
In a week? Or two weeks?
‫خلال أسبوع؟ أو اثنين؟‬
I can't wait!
‫لا أطيق الانتظار‬
Don't be ridiculous! Mankind has been doing this research for centuries,
‫يا لسخافتها، البشرية تقوم بهذه البحوث منذ عقود‬
but no one's ever succeeded!
‫ولكن لم ينجح أحد من قبل‬
Lick! Lick!
‫بيرورين بيرورين‬
Do you like it, Caesar-kun ?
‫هل يعجبك هذا يا سيزار-كن؟‬
It seems to be quite authentic, doesn't it?
‫يبدو أصليًّا بالكامل، أليس كذلك؟‬
The inside is exactly like the way it was, too. Lick!
‫الداخل مماثل للأصلي أيضًا‬
That's...
‫...هذا‬
No! Don't do that!
‫لا يعقل، توقف‬
This is fun.
‫هذا ممتع‬
Dammit!
‫سحقًا‬
We've arrived at Whole Cake Island.
‫لقد وصلنا إلى جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة‬
Wait! Hey, Black Leg!
‫انتظر يا ذا الساق السوداء‬
Give me back my heart before you go!
‫أعد لي قلبي قبل أن تغادر‬
Okay.
‫حسنًا‬
You only have two weeks to produce the gigantism drug!
‫لديك أسبوعان فقط لصنع عقار التضخيم‬
If it takes longer than that, I'll turn you into a candy man and lick you!
‫إن أخذ الأمر أطول من هذا، سأحولك إلى «رجل حلوى» وألعقك‬
I'll be killed in two weeks!
‫سأُقتَل بعد أسبوعين‬
I gotta do something!
‫يجب أن أفعل شيئًا ما‬
I've seen you dozens of times now.
‫كم من عشرات المرات رأيتك؟‬
It's you again.
‫أنت‬
I found another one.
‫وجدتُ آخر‬
There are so many of them!
‫هنالك العديد منهم‬
Anyway...
‫على أية حال‬
How did you guys multiply?!
‫كيف تضاعفتم يا رفاق؟‬